I spent a lot
of time thinking what
should I post on
my personal brand and
I was overcomplicating because
along with the journey
I was learning video
editing positioning
creating content
content pillars
AI automation
linkedin growth and strategies
and all this work
was just overcomplicating things
I thought I needed
to look professional
needed more polished videos
and I needed perfect
position and the worst
mistake is I thought
I needed I have
to look more experienced
to create content online
but I completely forgot
one because when you
start documenting online people
out there will actually
suggest some changes
give their opinions and
actually correct you in
your journey so that
those nuggets you can
actually pick and improve
your skills
your opinions and you
will learn a lot
of things while documenting
online while building a
personal brand and there
you go
your positioning gets clearer
as you document
as you get experienced
with what you are
doing that's exactly what
I am doing with
my own content
I am documenting what
I am learning
what I am testing
what works
what doesn't and what
I am building
I created a personal
brand experiment tracker to
help you what actually
build what you'll actually
build and what actually
you can track
Comment personal branding and
I will send it
to you